smartweb.com.ng 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy |smartweb

Smartweb Nigeria Limited. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of this website and the services offered by Smartweb. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Smartweb. (Smartweb) uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its website. 

#### Information We Collect

Smartweb may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for requesting information or ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. Some of the data we collect is information that identifies you personally, and may include your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone, payment account information, and other information necessary to provide the services requested. Smartweb also maintains a record of contacts for customer or technical support.

Smartweb may also collect information about how users access the website through log files and the use of cookies, and through third party services such as Mouseflow and Google Analytics. Such information may include standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on Smartweb's Web sites (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked)

#### What are Cookies?

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account.  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser's help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Smartweb to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by Smartweb to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on the Smartweb website do not contain personally identifiable information.  
More information about cookies can be found at [this link ](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)

#### Log Files

Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

#### How we Use and Share this information

Smartweb may use and share your personal information in order to provide the services requested. For example, your information may be provided to the domain registrar in order to process domain registrations, or with the relevant certificate authority to order an SSL certificate on your behalf. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations, and policies, and if your domains are not set to private registration, the publicly available WHOIS registry will contain personal information, including but not limited to your title, first name, surname, domain name, e-mail address, country, and phone number.

Smartweb is required to supply some of your personal data in order to request an SSL certificate from the certificate authority. By submitting a request for an SSL certificate order or renewal through Smartweb, you consent to Smartweb releasing all required personal information to the certificate authority in order to fulfill the request and you acknowledge and understand that Smartweb acts only as an intermediary between the customer and the certificate authority, in order to facilitate the order or renewal of the certificate. Smartweb has no influence on the outcome of an SSL certificate request and cannot guarantee that any request for an SSL certificate order or renewal will be granted.

Smartweb may also use the personally identifiable information collected by Smartweb to contact customers regarding products and services offered by Smartweb and, to the extent the user has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. We may also use this information and share it with trusted third parties for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts, including, without limitation, for purposes of customer reviews (such as for the utilization of programs like Google Seller Ratings). Smartweb will not sell or otherwise share this information with a third party for a third party marketing purposes, unless you specifically authorize such information sharing.

Smartweb may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case Smartweb is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

Smartweb may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by Smartweb from its customers. In all such cases, third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as Smartweb and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

Smartweb uses payment account information solely to check the financial qualifications of prospective Customers and to collect payment for the services provided by Smartweb.

#### Your Responsibility

You are responsible for the security of your Customer ID and passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others. Always remember to log out after your session ends to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home. You are also responsible for keeping your contact and payment information up to date. You may update or change your registration information by logging into the Smartweb Client Area. Certain information must be retained by Smartweb, even after termination of your account, in order for Smartweb to be able to provide the services requested, comply with its legal obligations, or to allow Smartweb to resolve disputes or enforce its agreements.

#### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Smartweb reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and such changes will be posted to the Smartweb website.
